<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Create...Inspire...Contribute]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Create...Inspire...Contribute]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/the-remix/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2016 12:33:43 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/the-remix/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Remix delivers great value for money]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>The Remix delivers great value for money</h1><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/8aa45ae0-b610-43fd-859f-0e4a391091be.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/the-remix/22679e3c-8ea1-46a7-aa13-f472d078cd98/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">22679e3c-8ea1-46a7-aa13-f472d078cd98</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2016 12:33:41 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[WHAT DOES THE REMIX PROGRAM ENTAIL]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>WHAT DOES THE REMIX PROGRAM ENTAIL</h1><p>So what is The Remix?</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/53be84fa-94d0-4cc2-9073-3b3d90034209.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/the-remix/what-does-the-remix-program-entail/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">8f35a870-fe20-4236-84e7-8d05bdb8aaa6</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2016 12:31:40 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[REMIX OUTCOMES]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>REMIX OUTCOMES</h1><p>THE REMIX delivers a range of immediate benefits to participating students, including:A safe, fun, creative and accessible activity, building hope, aspiration and a sense of social inclusion. Access to a positive and productive experience that provides an alternative to anti-social activity. A fun and engaging framework to develop trust, teamwork, leadership, self-confidence, creative self-expression, a sense of responsibility and commitment, and improved social skills. Opportunities to develop and express creativity and to share cultural stories as well as personal ideas, emotions and experiences with others. A better understanding of the potential that music and physical movement can offer as outlets for self-expression. Opportunities to develop new, portable skills in dance and other creative practices, reaffirming the student’s learning capacity, creativity and imagination. A dynamic, energising and motivating experience, developing a sense of responsibility, respect, self-worth, commitment and achievement. Renewed interest and engagement with school and the community, improving both educational outcomes and social cohesion. A voice, acknowledged presence and recognition in a positive context, both privately and publicly. A fun and engaging structure for beneficial exercise and motor skills development, improving fitness, co-ordination, concentration, muscle memory, mood and relaxation skills. A positive peer-focussed context, encouraging students to further develop skills in leadership, teamwork and organisation. Opportunities to develop relationships with positive role models, and to establish respectful and trusting relationships with caring adults. A safe and nurturing environment for exploration and self-discovery, and the opportunity to feel valued as part of a collaborative process and public performance. A highly visible, positive celebration of youth culture, providing access to safe community spaces and facilitating quality family time experiences. THE REMIX delivers a range of immediate benefits to participating students, including: Increased appreciation of the valuable role schools play in the community. Increased community cohesion, inclusion and engagement, breaking down long-standing barriers between and within marginalised communities. Social inclusion of marginalised young people. Improved awareness of alternative options for self expression and engagement with others. Improved skills across a broad range of areas. Production of public art works which give a voice to young people. Increased physical activity among young people (fitter, stronger, more agile, healthier teenagers). Increased potential for youth engagement with further education and training, opening career pathways (including striking success with disengaged and at-risk students). Decreased costs to welfare, public health and the justice system. Improved skills development for emerging youth leaders and social innovators, improving communication across community and government sectors to generate future youth relevant programming and activities.</p><img src="https://imgflo.herokuapp.com/graph/vahj1ThiexotieMo/98c8523401f31f4f188ea05406749048/croprotate.jpg?cropheight=1366&cropwidth=2048&degrees=0&input=https%3A%2F%2Fthe-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com%2F45571b3f-6c3a-4618-a091-254156146e01.jpg&x=0&y=0"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/45571b3f-6c3a-4618-a091-254156146e01.jpg</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">63e3e929-9d56-467b-83db-045433602ba5</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2016 12:20:20 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/ebb4cb08-faa2-486a-bc05-74d2c430f774.png">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/the-remix/5186381a-eec3-4789-b74f-4e64ca1df99a/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">5186381a-eec3-4789-b74f-4e64ca1df99a</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2016 12:03:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/bb735f4c-8ef0-4597-bc3b-5a05eee86825.png">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/the-remix/db9fdc95-d5e8-4346-8b5c-11d5873c0424/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">db9fdc95-d5e8-4346-8b5c-11d5873c0424</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2016 12:03:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/110a3445-23bc-4ed4-a781-2c8ae6b29302.png">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/the-remix/b5bdf806-2bb1-4647-8683-77d545340270/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">b5bdf806-2bb1-4647-8683-77d545340270</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2016 12:02:59 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>